<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IBAIS UNIVERSITY</string>
    <string name="large_text1">
        "IBAIS University IBAIS(International Business Administration and Information System) University is a Private and non-profit educational institution in Bangladesh. The Government of the People’s Republic of Bangladesh approved license to IBAIS University in August 2002 to function under the Private University Act of 1992 and as amended in 1998."
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Messages</string>
    <string name="large_text2">
        "Message from the Desk of the Chairman:"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text3">
        "To look back over our shoulder, IBAIS University was established in 2002 as an enterprise of IBAIS Limited, a Joint Stock Company, registered under the Company Act. In more than a decade, we have come a long way and we can be proud of our achievements. The full potentials however could not be exploited.
In the meantime, IBAIS University Trust has been established in line with the Private University Act 2010. The University has attained a new height under the dynamic leadership of professional Trustees. As required by the UGC, the management is taking effective measures to establish the University at its own land. We sincerely adhere to the Private University Act and the UGC rules and regulations to ensure professional conduct of the University affairs.
Located at the heart of Dhaka Metropolis, our University boasts of an array of renowned and resourceful teachers with unique academic background. Committed to quality education, IBAISU is a habitat of excellent academic environment. Our well-designed programs have opened a new vista of higher education to the learners to lead them to the most enviable position in life. All the departments of IBAIS University are unique in providing the best education through modern teaching methods.
Like other facilities, the University library is also full of latest books and journals. Teachers and students are found to swarm around the library spending hours together. Our Labs are equipped with latest facilities to meet the demand of the teachers and the students.
This Prospectus is published mainly for the Students, the Guardians, and the Academics who can easily focus on different modules and programs of the University. It also contains a brief outline of the University, its Faculties and how the administration works.  I am confident that it will be of great help to the students, parents, media, and academics to make an overall appraisal of the University.
Welcome to the world of IBAIS University. We are all set to make a history and march ahead to a still brighter level of success.
        Showkat Aziz (Russell)
        Vice-Chairman
        Board of Trustees"
    </string>
    
    <string name="large_text4">
        "Message from the Vice-Chancellor(Designate):"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text5">
        "Dear Students,
It is my pleasure to welcome you to the International Business Administration and Information System (IBAIS) University. It is one of the pioneering and front ranking private universities of Bangladesh. Its primary mission is to impart and disseminate relevant, appropriate, and quality education to our promising young generation. I appreciate your decision to select IBAIS University as your academic home for higher education.
IBAIS University ensures the students uninterrupted, meaningful, pragmatic, and job-oriented education. I am happy that these qualities are observed and acclaimed by your caring parents and guardians. As we continue our relentless efforts to making IBAISU an excellent institution, we can hope that more students will choose this university to have higher education in a congenial environment.
Under the inspired guidance of the new management and dynamic leadership of Mr. Showkat Aziz (Russell), IBAIS University is progressing in a determined way towards the coveted excellence and you students are our comrades in this noble venture. God-willing, we will soon have our exclusive permanent facilities built on our own land.
Our undergraduate and postgraduate programs aim to prepare our students for this increasingly global and highly competitive world. The courses offered are IT, Computer Science, Electrical and Computer Engineering, Electrical and Electronic Engineering, Business Administration, Economics, Tourism and Hotel Management, English Literature, Business English, and Honors in Law. In addition, we plan to introduce two-year law course very soon. IBAIS University has rich library and lab facilities to conduct practical classes.
We try to develop students’ potential and expand their horizons through co-curricular activities such as seminars, workshops, symposiums, debates, cultural events, and educational tours. These add to their maturity and prepare them to make valuable contribution to our nation building efforts. We graciously invite you to IBAIS University family and to see what our highly qualified and skilled faculties can offer to make your academic life fruitful and enjoyable. We are always ready to receive you with open hearts and guide you to attain your goals.
Learn, work diligently, and thrive!  I wish you all the very best.
        Professor Dr. M. Delwar Hussain"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text6">
        "Message from the Vice-Chairman:"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text7">
        "It’s a great delight for me to welcome you to the IBAIS (International Business Administration and Information System) University, a leading private sector University in Bangladesh.
 In the present scenario of Bangladesh, choosing the right university is one of the most challenging decisions you will have to take. If you carefully compare your choices, you will find real differences among universities and those differences are vital. The university you will choose should match your goals, your values and your vision.
Academic programs of IBAIS University are organized under three faculties in seven departments. These are English, Law, Tourism and Hotel Management., Electrical and Electronic Engineering, Computer Science and Engineering, Business Administration and Economics.
In reviewing our prospectus, you will see broad range of educational opportunities offered here. Our programs emphasize hand-on learning as a way to build your skills better. This university strives to provide quality education at moderate cost to meet the global demand. You can be sure that the IBAIS University is one of the most dynamic institutions in Bangladesh.
If you go through the general information of IBAIS University, you will find the goals, mission, guiding values, challenges, and scope of the University.
In conclusion, I would like to assure the students that it is our goal to enable them to enter the world as a leader who will make a difference in everything that they encounter in their future professional life. I hope at IBAIS University the students will attain all that they dream of.
        M. Kawser H. Comet
        Vice-Chairman
        Board of Trustees"
    </string>

    <string name="large_text8">
        "Message from the Pro Vice-Chancellor(Designate):"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text9">
        "It is my profound honor and privilege to welcome you all on behalf of IBAIS University, an institution which has already proved its status as a place for higher education and research. As Education is the prime concern of any country, IBAIS University has got all the potential to become a center of excellence. The IBAIS University authority, Faculty members and Administration are sincere enough to impart quality higher education. This sincerity is reflected in the syllabuses and curricula of different disciplines on which we provide appropriate modern education.\n"
        "In the present day world as always, knowledge rather than physical resources is the main driver of development. And IBAIS University can be considered as a true center of excellence. Our University has been pleased to contribute to the shaping of government’s policy on ways in which higher education can play a key role in the creation of a peaceful and prosperous country. What makes it so special is the true enthusiasm of the students. It is in this very context of wisdom conservation, knowledge generation, intellectual participation and partnership, IBAIS University endeavors its best to introduce a series of modern, innovative and conventional academic programs.\n"
        "The students organize and participate in different programs and festivals all over the year, which help them grow as true citizens of the country and the globe. They also participate in different social activities. Sincere attention is given to all and they have already proved their worth both in national and international job markets. The main idea is to go on generating critical masses that would blend with the newer frontiers of knowledge and lead the nation to global heights. We are very conscious in taking appropriate steps for the uplift of overall education level of the university to keep pace with the ever changing world of knowledge and wisdom.
        Professor Dr. Engr.Md.Humayn Kabir"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_main3">University Profile</string>
    <string name="large_text10">
        "PREAMBLE"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text11">
        "IBAIS University (International Business Administration and Information System University) is a private and non-profit university functioning under the Private University Act of 1992 as amended in 1998 and 2010.Founded under the auspicious of IBAIS Ltd (a Joint Stock Company) in August, 2002. IBAIS University follows the curriculum and pedagogy of North America and is committed to global standard, which is reflected in our academic policies and curricula.
 IBAIS University since its inception has been committed to provide students with undergraduate and graduate programs with the right combination of all the essential components required for attaining excellence in learning for those who are eligible to pursue advanced degrees in any modern country of the globe. Here, we are committed to help the learners become responsible and caring citizens. It strives to turn an individual into an effective professional through developing one’s innate potentials and interests. Freedom, Creativity and Service all these are combined to produce leaders of the society capable of meeting challenges of the new era. Here, the programs of all the disciplines are global, which tend to summation of conceptual, applied and computer oriented learning. Our programs are competitively priced making accessible to the middle class and leading to producing fast-track graduates."
    </string>
    <string name="large_text12">
        "MISSION"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text13">
        "IBAIS University is committed to providing quality and excellent academic programs of global standard responsive to the emerging challenges of the rapid technological advancement at reasonable cost. The University is dedicated to pursue these programs so that the students who desire to develop and exploit their potentialities have the opportunity to do so. Respect for the intellectual potential and dignity of students as individual human beings, without prejudice to their racial, ethnic or cultural background, shall be paramount in all the academic and other activities of the University."
    </string>
    <string name="large_text14">
        "GOALS"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text15">
        "The goal of the IBAIS University is to impart an excellent broad based education with a focus on professional development, in order to equip the students with appropriate modern knowledge and skill necessary for leading the country in its quest for development.

 The major goals of IBAIS University are:

•	To pursue vigorous improvements in the quality of higher education through dedicated commitment to teaching, training and research.

•	To create a congenial academic environment for the youth, free from political and other disturbances for their intellectual advancement.

•	To help flourish quality, talent and skill of individual students to enable them to lead a successful life as professionals and responsible citizens.

•	To provide specialized and high quality education for employment in positions of responsibility across a wide range of IT and Business, Social and Public organizations all over the world.

•	To make provisions for imparting education at globally recognized level with a view to getting accreditation of degrees by prestigious International Accreditation bodies.

•	To use modern instructional techniques and technology to the best advantage so as to enhance and enrich students’ achievements for fulfilling their educational and career goals as well as contributing to socio-economic development of the country.

•	To provide educational opportunities to persons already employed or engaged in business allowing them to pursue undergraduate and graduate programs without interrupting their career and without any compromise on quality."
    </string>
    <string name="large_text16">
        "ACCREDITATION AND COLLABORATION"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text17">
        "The IBAIS University is accredited by the Government of the People’s Republic of Bangladesh, and its curricula and programs have been approved by the Bangladesh University Grants Commission. The Honorable President of the People’s Republic of Bangladesh is the Chancellor of IBAIS University"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text18">
        "The IBAIS University has collaborations with the following universities"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text19">
        "The University of Michigan-Flint, USA , City University, New York, USA , North Eastern University, Boston, USA,  Texas A and M International University, USA, St. Edward University, Texas ,USA , The University of Greenwich, UK,  Central Queensland University, Australia ,  Ballarat University, Melbourne, Australia ,  The University of Bedfordshire, UK, Bangkok University, Thailand , Deakin University, Australia, Edith Cowan University, Perth, Australia, University of Abertay Dundee, Scotland, UK, St. Petersburg State Technical University, Russia, College of Tourism and Hotel Management, Cyprus, The European College of Graduate Studies, Germany, Institute of Hospitality Management, Ireland, Melbourne Institute of Technology, Australia, Kingston College, Canada and  a number of other well-known universities in the USA, Canada, UK and Australia."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_main4">Faculties and Programs</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main5">Admission Information</string>
    <string name="large_text20">
        "ADMISSION REQUIREMENTS
UNDERGRADUATE AND GRADUATE PROGRAMS"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_main6">Chancellor</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main7">MainActivity7</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main8">MainActivity8</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main9">MainActivity9</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main10">MainActivity10</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main11">MainActivity11</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main12">MainActivity12</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main13">MainActivity13</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main14">MainActivity14</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main15">MainActivity15</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main16">MainActivity16</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main17">MainActivity17</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main18">Student Portal</string>
    <string name="large_text68">
    "Student Login:"
    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_main19">MainActivity19</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main20">MainActivity20</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main21">Thankful</string>
    <string name="large_text64">
        "Special Thanks To:"
    </string>

    <string name="large_text65">
        "Dr. Md.Akther Hossain\n"
        "Head, Dept. of Computer Science and Engineering"
    </string>

    <string name="large_text66">
        "Md.Shisir Mia\n"
        "Lecturer,Dept. of Computer Science and Engineering"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text67">
        "Mr.Md.Atiquir Rahaman\n"
        "System Administrator\n"
        "IT Division"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_main22">MainActivity22</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main23">MainActivity23</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main24">MainActivity24</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main25">MainActivity25</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main26">MainActivity26</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main27">MainActivity27</string>
    <string name="large_text45">
        "Department of Computer Science and Engineering"
        </string>
    <string name="large_text54">
        "Prof.Dr.Matiur Rahaman Mian\n"
        "Dean\n"
        "Faculty of Science and Engineering\n"
        "Former Director,Institute of Scientific Instrumentation\n"
        "University Grants Commission of Bangladesh"
    </string>
<string name="large_text46">
    "Dr. Md. Akter Hossain\n"
    "Head\n"
    "Dept. of CSE"
</string>

    <string name="large_text69">
        "Md.Shisir Mia\n"
        "Lecturer,Dept. of Computer Science and Engineering"
    </string>

<string name="large_text47">
    "Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering"
</string>
    <string name="large_text48">
    "Mr. S. M. Farhaduzzaman Azad\n"
    "Coordinator\n"
    "Dept. of EEE"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_main28">MainActivity28</string>

    <string name="large_text49">
        "Department of Business Administration"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text50">
        "Prof. Dr.M.Nasim Anjum\n"
        "Former Dean,Faculty of Business Administration\n"
        "Director,IBA, University of Rajshahi"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text51">
        "Professor Dr.  Arifur Rahman\n"
        "Head\n"
        "Department of Business Administration"
    </string>

    <string name="large_text52">
        "Department of Economics"
    </string>

    <string name="large_text53">
        "Dr. Muhammad Farid Uddin\n"
        "Head\n"
        "Department of Economics"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_main29">MainActivity29</string>

    <string name="large_text55">
        "Department of Law"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text56">
        "Prof.Dr.Belal Husain Joy\n"
        "Dean,Faculty of Humanities and Law\n"
        "Barrister-at-Law and Arbitrator\n"
        "Bangladesh Supreme Court"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text57">
        "Ms. Shammi Aktar\n"
        "Coordinator\n"
        "Dept. of Law"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text58">
        "Department of Tourism and Hotel Management"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text59">
        "Professor Mohammed Ahsan Ullah\n"
                   "Head\n"
        "Head,Dept. of Tourism and Hotel Management\n"
        "Former Principal,ATAB Tourism Training Institute\n"
        "Former Principal,National Hotel and Tourism Training Institute\n"
        "Bangladesh Parjatan Corporation"
    </string>

    <string name="large_text60">
        "Department of English"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text61">
        "Ms.Farzana Parvin\n"
        "Head,Department of English"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_main30">MainActivity30</string>

    <string name="large_text62">
        "Center for Training and Research"
    </string>

    <string name="large_text63">
    "Professor Dr. Sujit Saha\n"
    "Director "
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_main31">MainActivity31</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main32">MainActivity32</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main33">MainActivity33</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main34">MainActivity34</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main35">Graduate Programs</string>
    <string name="large_text70">
        "FACULTY OF SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text71">
        "MSCS(Direct)"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text72">
        "B.Sc. in CS/CSE/IT or equivalent."
    </string>
    <string name="large_text73">
        "MSCS (Executive)"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text74">
        "B.Sc. in Engineering/Mathematics / Statistics/Physics/Applied Physics/ Electronic or minimum Bachelor Degree with Diploma in Computer Science/Engineering or 4 years of working experiences in relevant fields."
    </string>
    <string name="large_text75">
        "MSCS(Pre-requisite)"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text76">
        "Minimum Bachelor Degree with computer literacy."
    </string>
    <string name="large_text77">
        "MSCSE"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text78">
        "B.Sc. in Computer Science and Engineering."
    </string>
    <string name="large_text79">
        "FACULTY OF BUSINESS AND ECONOMICS"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text80">
        "MBA (Direct)"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text81">
        "BBA/M.Com/Bachelor’s Degree with Post Graduate Diploma in MGT/FIN/MKT/ACT/PMGT."
    </string>
    <string name="large_text82">
        "MBA(Executive)"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text83">
        ""B.Com. (Honors)/Master’s/B.Sc.Engineering/ MBBS or Bachelor Degree with 4 years of experiences in relevant fields.
    </string>
    <string name="large_text84">
        "MBA(Pre-requisite)"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text85">
        "BA/B.Com/B.Sc. or its equivalent."
    </string>
    <string name="large_text86">
        "FACULTY OF HUMANITIES AND LAW"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text87">
        "MA in English(01 Year)"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text88">
        "Minimum CGPA 2.5 in Bachelor Degree in English Literature/Language/Applied Linguistics/TEFL/TESL/TESOL or an equivalent degree from an approved university."
    </string>
    <string name="large_text89">
        "MA in English(02 years)"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text90">
        "Students having Graduation from any discipline."
    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_main36">MainActivity36</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_image">ViewImage</string>

</resources>
